instantdollarz.com 2008-06-23

# Privacy Policy: InstantDollarz Media

**PRIVACY POLICY**

InstantDollarz Inc. and its affiliated and subsidiary companies and sites (hereafter referred to as "InstantDollarz") recognize that its customers, visitors, and other users of the site and any co-branded, mirrored, or successor sites (collectively or individually “You” or “Your”) value their privacy. This Privacy Policy provides important details about the privacy policies and practices of InstantDollarz's corporate site www.InstantDollarz.com ("InstantDollarz Site"). 

Revision Date: June 7, 2007 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the InstantDollarz.com’s Terms of Use. Your use of the InstantDollarz.com Site remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. InstantDollarz reserves the right to change or modify this policy at any time, with any change being effective immediately upon posting on this website. InstantDollarz is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will collect and use information throughout this website only as described in this Privacy Policy. By using this Site, You signify Your acceptance of this Policy. If You do not agree to the terms of this Policy, in whole or part, You may not use this Site. 

I. INFORMATION COLLECTION 

InstantDollarz is the corporate entity that manages the InstantDollarz marketing and technology companies. The InstantDollarz site is not directed towards individual Internet consumers nor does it seek any personally identifiable information ("PII") from such consumers. PII may be collected should a consumer contact InstantDollarz on his/her own accord and volunteer PII. 

**Log File Information** : Like many websites, we gather information about how visitors use this Website. In general, all web pages on this Website can be visited without telling us who You are or revealing any personal information about Yourself. Our servers will automatically log certain access details for each visitor including domain, IP address, time of access, browser version, referring site and content visited. This information cannot be used to identify You personally. We also collect information about Your activities on and through this Website from our third party business associates, suppliers, vendors and other agents. Aside from these web statistics, You will remain anonymous unless You voluntarily provide us with personally identifiable information ("PII") during this visit or any previous visit. 

**Web Beacons** : Web beacons are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. Such beacons may be used in emails sent to You to track which emails are opened by You. 

II. USE OF INFORMATION 

InstantDollarz reserves the right to use information gathered on the InstantDollarz site as follows: 

  * We use web beacons and log file information to: (a) provide more applicable content and information; (b) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (c) monitor aggregate numbers of visitors, pages viewed, etc.
  * We may also retain any emails, letters, or other correspondence between You and InstantDollarz to ensure quality control and improve service. 

III. INFORMATION MANAGEMENT 

InstantDollarz may share information with affiliated entities in connection with the sale, reorganization, liquidation or transfer of any of the InstantDollarz properties. InstantDollarz may also release information in reponse to legal subpoenas, court orders and other judicial claims; to enforce our Privacy Policy, terms and conditions or any other agreements; to contact, identify or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with our or others’ rights or property, including but not limited to claims for infringement of intellectual property, invasion of privacy, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person; and to assist other companies in fraud protection or investigation. 

IV. THIRD PARTY OFFERS 

This Site may contain links to other sites not owned by InstantDollarz. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, or the services or representations made by third-party advertisers. Navigation using these links constitutes acknowledgement of this fact. This privacy statement also only covers any actions made by InstantDollarz, and NOT any actions of advertisers OR ad servers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. This privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

V. DATA SECURITY 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, InstantDollarz uses commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard confidentiality of all data stored on our servers. We use appropriate industry standard security measures including firewalls, encryptions, token authentication, monitoring technology and continuous adaptive analysis of network traffic to track any and all abuse of network properties and data. All data stored on InstantDollarz servers are treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. Access to any PII is limited to the working personnel of InstantDollarz who are authorized to access such systems, and are required to keep this information confidential. While our data management practices are held to these standards at all times, no data transaction on the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion. 

VI. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY 

InstantDollarz makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. None of InstantDollarz's products and services, and neither the InstantDollarz Site, are developed for or directed at children, and we have made commercially reasonable efforts to prevent our knowing acceptance of any such information from children under the age of 18. It is possible that by some error or deception, we may receive information regarding or from children under the age of 18. If notified, we will verify the information and obtain parental consent immediately, or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If You believe Your child has provided InstantDollarz with any personally identifiable data by some interaction at InstantDollarz, please contact support@instantdollarz.com to have them removed. 

VI. EMAIL MARKETING PRACTICES and DATA PROCESSING 

InstantDollarz is committed to proper Internet practices and full compliance with the United States' CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. § 7701) and the European Union's Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations of 2003 through usage of the [Safe Harbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor) principle. It is our policy to prohibit the sending of unsolicited or "Spam" email by InstantDollarz or any of its marketing partners. By providing information to InstantDollarz, you acknowledge that they operate in the United States and agree to (i) permit InstantDollarz to transmit and use your User information anywhere necessary, including across international boundaries, to affect the services and transactions provided by this Site; and (ii) that such use by InstantDollarz shall be subject to the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Policy and applicable Terms of Use. 

VIII. ENDNOTE 

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this site, please contact us at support@instantdollarz.com, or use the mailing address listed below. We welcome Your questions, comments, and concerns about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. Please send us feedback pertaining to these matters or any other issue You may have with InstantDollarz. If You feel that we are not following our stated Privacy Policy, You may contact the Better Business Bureau, Your local consumer protection office, or the Federal Trade Commission. 

IX. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS. 

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to support@instantdollarz.com or write us: 

InstantDollarz.com   
PO BOX 17257   
Philadelphia, PA 19105 

X. ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY. 

Your use of the InstantDollarz sites, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and InstantDollarz’s Terms of Use. By using these InstantDollarz sites, You are accepting the practices set out in this privacy policy and the terms of use. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the top of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since You last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of the InstantDollarz sites following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute Your acceptance of the changes.
